https://www.nufcblog.com/privacy/

The Newcastle United Blog
Ed Harrison'sThe Newcastle United Blog
PrivacyThe Newcastle United Blog knows that you care about how your personal information is used and shared, and we take your privacy very seriously.Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.This Privacy Policy covers The Newcastle United Blog’s treatment of personal information that The Newcastle United Blog gathers when you are on the The Newcastle United Blog website and when you use The Newcastle United Blog services. This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that The Newcastle United Blog does not own or control, or to individuals that The Newcastle United Blog does not employ or manage.Information Collected by The Newcastle United BlogWe only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. This information allows us to provide you with a customized and efficient experience. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with this objective. We collect the following types of information from our The Newcastle United Blog  users:1. Information You Provide to Us: o  We receive and store any information you enter on our website or provide to us in any other way. You can choose not to provide us with certain information, but then you may not be able to take advantage of many of our special features.2. Automatic Information: o  We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. The Newcastle United Blog and its authorized agents automatically receive and record certain “traffic data” on their server logs from your browser including your IP address, The Newcastle United Blog cookie information, and the page you requested. The Newcastle United Blog uses this traffic data to help diagnose problems with its servers, analyze trends and administer the website. o The Newcastle United Blog may collect and, on any page, display the total counts that page has been viewed. o Many companies offer programs that help you to visit websites anonymously. While The Newcastle United Blog will not be able to provide you with a personalized experience if we cannot recognize you, we want you to be aware that these programs are available.E-mail CommunicationsThe Newcastle United Blog is very concerned about your privacy and we will never provide your email address to a third party without your explicit permission, as detailed in the “Sharing Your Information” section below. The Newcastle United Blog may send out e-mails with The Newcastle United Blog-related news, products, offers, surveys or promotions.CookiesCookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. The Newcastle United Blog cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or e-mail address is.The “help” portion of the toolbar on the majority of browsers will direct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to command the browser to tell you when you receive a new cookie, or how to fully disable cookies. We recommend that you leave the cookies activated because cookies allow you to use some of  The Newcastle United Blog’s coolest features.The Newcastle United Blog’s advertising partners may place a cookie on your browser that makes it possible to collect anonymous non-personally identifiable information that ad delivery systems use to present more relevant ads. If you would prefer to opt-out of this standard practice, please visit our advertising partner Platform-A’s privacy policy and opt-out page.Sharing Your InformationRest assured that we neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone and that we will share your personal information only as described below.The Newcastle United Blog Personnel:The Newcastle United Blog personnel and authorized consultants and/or contractors may have access to user information if necessary in the normal course of The Newcastle United Blog business.Business Transfers:In some cases, we may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the business assets that is transferred. Moreover, if The Newcastle United Blog, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred.Protection of The Newcastle United Blog and Others:We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with a law; to enforce or apply our Terms of Use and other policies; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of The Newcastle United Blog, our employees, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Syndication:The Newcastle United Blog allows for the RSS syndication of all of its public content within the The Newcastle United Blog website. With Your Consent: Except as noted above, we will contact you when your personal information is shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to opt out to prevent the sharing of this information.Children Under 18 Years of AgeYou must be 13 years and older to register to use the The Newcastle United Blog website. As a result, The Newcastle United Blog does not specifically collect information about children. If we learn that The Newcastle United Blog has collected information from a child under the age of 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. We recommend that minors between the ages of 13 and 18 ask and receive their parents’ permission before using The Newcastle United Blog or sending information about themselves or anyone else over the Internet.Changes to this Privacy PolicyThe Newcastle United Blog may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, at its sole discretion. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used. If we make changes to the Privacy Policy, we will notify you by posting an announcement on the The Newcastle United Blog website so you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances if any, it is disclosed.Conditions of UseIf you decide to visit The Newcastle United Blog website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.Effective Date of this Privacy Policy – This Privacy Policy is effective as of September, 2010.News Nowsearch PollsHow Will Newcastle Fare Against West Brom On Saturday? Win Lose Draw
View Results Loading ...Last 5 ResultsDateTeamResult10/25Wolves – AwayD 1-111/1Everton – HomeW 2-111/5Southampton – AwayL 2-011/21Chelsea – HomeL 2-011/27Crystal Palace – AwayW 2-0Next 5 GamesDateTeamLocation12/12: 15:00West BromHome12/16: 18:00LeedsAway12/19: 20:00FulhamHome12/22: 17:30Brentford (League Cup)Away12/26: 20:00Man CityAwayLeague PositionPosTeamGamesGDPoints9Everton1121710Wolves11-41711Crystal Palace1111612Aston Villa971513Newcastle10-31414Leeds11-41415Arsenal11-41316Brighton11-310Goalscorers – 2020-2021 SeasonPlayerLeagueCupsTotalWilson77Joelinton123Murphy112Hendrick11Fraser11Almiron11Hayden11Lascelles11Ritchie11Shelvey11Saint-Maximin11ads
Newcastle United Blog – One Of The BestThe Newcastle United Blog has been chosen as one of the best overall Newcastle blogs – click on the picture below for more information.Please Follow Us
MENUHomeAuthorContactAdvertisePrivacyhealth update 14 June, 2020 I had three cat scans and a full body bone scan two weeks ago to check on the spread of my prostate cancer.The cancer is still progressing, but the rate of progression has been slowed by the addional medication I have been prescribed - XTANDI.Stage four prostate cancer is terminal, but I hope to be around for a while yet.It is as it is.I was diagnosed with protate cancer in April, 2011 and it became stage four in late December, 2016That's when it spread through the bones to several areas of the body.Dr. Dhruva and the nurses and staff at the Rex Cancer Center in Raleigh, North Carolina have been fantastic.They deserve great credit - they are my heroes in this world.Ed HarrisonMadeline HarrisonMilo HarrisonKacper Tylenda Website DesignerOne of our avid readers Kacper Tylenda from Poland was the person who came in during April, 2017 and redesigned this web-site from top to bottom.We think he did a fantastic job to modernize the site with the roll-out on Thursday May 18th surprisingly smooth.I am so appreciative of his help.Kacper is starting his own business in web-design so if you want a website built or know of people who want to redo their sites in any way.Here is Kacper’s LinkedIn profile.
